{
    "Q1": {
        "question": "I'm very happy _____ in India. I really miss being there. ",
        "options": {
            "a": "to live",
            "b": "to have lived",
            "c": "to be lived",
            "d": "to be living"
        },
        "answer": "b"
    },
    "Q2": {
        "question": "They didn't reach an agreement ______ their differences.",
        "options": {
            "a": "on account of",
            "b": "due",
            "c": "because",
            "d": "owing"
        },
        "answer": "a"
    },
    "Q3": {
        "question": "I wish I _____ those words. But now it's too late.",
        "options": {
            "a": "not having said",
            "b": "have never said",
            "c": "never said",
            "d": "had never said"
        },
        "answer": "d"
    },
    "Q4": {
        "question": "The woman, who has been missing for 10 days, is believed _____.",
        "options": {
            "a": "to be abducted",
            "b": "to be abducting",
            "c": "to have been abducted",
            "d": "to have been abducting"
        },
        "answer": "c"
    },
    "Q5": {
        "question": "She was working on her computer with her baby next to _____.",
        "options": {
            "a": "herself",
            "b": "her",
            "c": "her own",
            "d": "hers"
        },
        "answer": "b"
    },
    "Q6": {
        "question": "_____ to offend anyone, she said both cakes were equally good.",
        "options": {
            "a": "Not wanting",
            "b": "As not wanting",
            "c": "She didn't want",
            "d": "Because not wanting"
        },
        "answer": "a"
    },
    "Q7": {
        "question": "_____ in trying to solve this problem. It's clearly unsolvable.",
        "options": {
            "a": "There's no point",
            "b": "It's no point",
            "c": "There isn't point",
            "d": "It's no need"
        },
        "answer": "a"
    },
    "Q8": {
        "question": "Last year, when I last met her, she told me she _____ a letter every day for the last two months.",
        "options": {
            "a": "had written",
            "b": "has written",
            "c": "had been writing",
            "d": "wrote"
        },
        "answer": "c"
    },
    "Q9": {
        "question": "He _____ robbed as he was walking out of the bank.",
        "options": {
            "a": "had",
            "b": "did",
            "c": "got",
            "d": "were"
        },
        "answer": "c"
    },
    "Q10": {
        "question": "_____ forced to do anything. He acted of his own free will.",
        "options": {
            "a": "In no way was he",
            "b": "No way he was",
            "c": "In any way he was",
            "d": "In any way was he"
        },
        "answer": "a"
    },
    "Q11": {
        "question": "It _____ the best idea to pay for those tickets by credit card. It was too risky.",
        "options": {
            "a": "may not have been",
            "b": "may not be",
            "c": "might not be",
            "d": "must not have been"
        },
        "answer": "a"
    },
    "Q12": {
        "question": "They _____ in the basement for three months.",
        "options": {
            "a": "were made sleeping",
            "b": "were made sleep",
            "c": "were made to sleep",
            "d": "made to sleep"
        },
        "answer": "c"
    },
    "Q13": {
        "question": "We'll never know what might have happened _____ the email earlier.",
        "options": {
            "a": "if he sent",
            "b": "had he sent",
            "c": "if he has sent",
            "d": "did he sent"
        },
        "answer": "b"
    },
    "Q14": {
        "question": "If success _____, we need to prepare ourselves for every possible scenario.",
        "options": {
            "a": "is to be achieved",
            "b": "is achieved",
            "c": "will be achieved",
            "d": "is due to achieve"
        },
        "answer": "a"
    },
    "Q15": {
        "question": "______ gifts to the judges.",
        "options": {
            "a": "It's not allowed offering",
            "b": "It's not permitted to offer",
            "c": "It's not permitted offering",
            "d": "It's not allowed to offer"
        },
        "answer": "b"
    },
    "Q16": {
        "question": "I ______ bus on Mondays.",
        "options": {
            "a": "'m going to work with",
            "b": "'m going to work by",
            "c": "go to work with",
            "d": "go to work by"
        },
        "answer": "d"
    },
    "Q17": {
        "question": "Sorry, but this chair is ______.",
        "options": {
            "a": "me",
            "b": "mine",
            "c": "my",
            "d": "our"
        },
        "answer": "b"
    },
    "Q18": {
        "question": "I ______ to the cinema.",
        "options": {
            "a": "not usually go",
            "b": "don't usually go",
            "c": "don't go usually",
            "d": "do not go usually"
        },
        "answer": "b"
    },
    "Q19": {
        "question": "Where ______ ?",
        "options": {
            "a": "your sister works",
            "b": "your sister work",
            "c": "does your sister work",
            "d": "do your sister work"
        },
        "answer": "c"
    },
    "Q20": {
        "question": "The test is ______ February.",
        "options": {
            "a": "in",
            "b": "at",
            "c": "on",
            "d": "over"
        },
        "answer": "a"
    }
}